<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="changelog.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<log>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-05-17 13:05 +0900" rev="1175">
		<new rev="1167,1169">KMNanonisConcatMultipass is added. This concatenates 2D waves taken by the multipass mode of Nanonis into a single 3D wave. Move to the datafolder where the multipass waves are and choose &#34;KM &#62; Nanonis tools &#62; Concatenate multipass waves&#34;. </new>
	 	<new rev="1166">A default mode of height can be specifed from the preference.</new>
		<chg rev="1167-1169">The menu item to make a log wave of 3ds files was moved under &#34;KM &#62; Nanonis tools&#34;</chg>
		<chg rev="1156-1158,1160,1161">Some modifications of LineSpectra and LineProfile.
			<sub>
				<item>A waterfall plot, instead of traces with offset, is used in the panels for better handling of hidden lines and unevenly spaced biases. &#34;axlen&#34; in the panels is a keyword of ModifyWaterfall, which is an Igor Pro command used for the waterfall plot. See the help of ModifyWaterfall for details.</item>
				<item>The option to save 1D waves was deleted. The output wave is a 2D wave. To make a waterfall plot from a 2D wave, choose &#34;Windows &#62; New &#62; Packages &#62; Waterfall Plot&#34; or &#34;KM &#62; Display &#62; Selected Wave as Traces&#34; with a 2D wave selected in the Data Browser. The latter is equivalent to plot many 1D waves.</item>
			</sub>
		</chg>
		<chg rev="1163,1165,1170-1175">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1159,1162">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-05-10 14:10 +0900" rev="1155">
		<chg rev="1154">The error handling of KMColor was modified. A color table wave is loaded as long as a path to the wave is given as supposed to be.</chg>
		<chg rev="1151-1153,1155">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1150">The index is now correctly reflected when the information bar of LayerViewer is reopened.</bug>
		<bug rev="1149">Improved backword compatibility in opening a file created by Igor 6.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-05-02 19:30 +0900" rev="1148">
		<bug rev="1148">Fixed a bug that an exception was raised when some keyboard shortcuts were used.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-05-01 18:30 +0900" rev="1147">
		<chg rev="1146">Some modes of subtraction were reverted by request.</chg>
		<chg rev="1145">Real only/imaginary only/magnitude/phase in radian can be chosen from SpectrumViewer as well as LayerViewer. The shortcut is the same (X).</chg>
		<chg rev="1144,1147">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1143">Fixed an error of LineProfile and LineSpectra. The error occured when a target window was a window in which the source wave is not displayed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-04-26 15:50 +0900" rev="1142">
		<chg rev="1139-1141">Some shortcuts were changed to be assigned in a coherent way. The changed shortcuts are /, c, t, x, and C. For detail, see <a href="http://www.riken.jp/epmrt/kohsaka/km/shortcuts.pdf">the cheet sheet of shortcuts</a>.</chg>
		<bug rev="1142">Fixed a bug that &#34;KM &#62; Load Data...  &#62; Load Data from a Folder&#34; did not work correctly for a folder containing a file for which no loader function is prepared (e.g., Nanonis-Session.ini).</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-04-24 16:45 +0900" rev="1138">
		<chg rev="1136,1138">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="1135">Obsolute modes of subtraction were deleted.</chg>
		<bug rev="1131-1134,1137">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-04-19 14:15 +0900" rev="1130">
		<chg rev="1130">Collecting header information from Nanonis 3ds files, which was implimented in rev. 721, can be done from &#34;KM &#62; Load Data... &#62; Nanonis 3ds log&#34;. By selecting a folder, 3ds files under the folder are recursively searched and header information is collected.</chg>
		<chg rev="1127-1129">Small modifications.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-04-05 15:50 +0900" rev="1126">
		<chg rev="1118">&#34;Move Windows In&#34; was deleted because the same thing can be done from &#34;Windows &#62; Control &#62; Retrieve All Windows&#34;</chg>
		<bug rev="1121,1122">Some waves with generic names (e.g. color, list, mask) are now not used inside of the macro to avoid conflict of names.</bug>
		<bug rev="1123-1126">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-02-15 16:50 +0900" rev="1117">
		<bug rev="1117">Fixed a bug that LineSubtraction did not work.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2018-02-08 20:45 +0900" rev="1116">
		<chg rev="1112">Histogram now works for complex waves.</chg>
		<chg rev="1111">The menu items for analysis in the main menu (e.g. KM > Subtract) were deleted. These are obsolete and slow down menu response when many waves exist in the current datafolder.</chg>
		<chg rev="1113-1116">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1110">Fixed code causing crash of Igor Pro.</bug>
		<bug rev="1109">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-12-28 13:55 +0900" rev="1108">
		<bug rev="1108">The coordinates of the mouse cursor was not correctly acquired when waves with different x- and y-scaling values were displayed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-12-04 12:50 +0900" rev="1107">
		<chg rev="1102,1103,1106,1107">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1104,1105">The panels of Line Spectra and Line Profile now correctly work for linecut data.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-10-26 21:15 +0900" rev="1101">
		<bug rev="1101">Fixed a bug that Spectrum Viewer did not correctly show a spectrum.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-09-15 16:15 +0900" rev="1099">
		<chg rev="1099">The positive sign (+) can be added to the auto-annotation text.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-09-14 18:30 +0900" rev="1098">
		<chg rev="1094,1097,1098">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="1092,1093,1095,1096">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-09-05 17:55 +0900" rev="1090">
		<bug rev="1087-1090">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-08-04 15:20 +0900" rev="1086">
		<new rev="1086">Requires Igor Pro ver. 7.05.</new>
		<new rev="1012,1075-1078">LayerViewer supports making a movie. Right-click the control bar area and select the menu of &#34;Save/Export Graphics &#62; Save Graphics (Movie) ...&#34;</new>
		<new rev="1000-1005,1007-1009,1055-1061,1064,1067-1070">Now Line Profile and Line Spectra support complex waves.</new>
		<new rev="968,972,1040">149 color table waves are added.</new>
		<new rev="944,946,948,949,950,952-955,965,967,973,974,1028,1036,1037,1043,1046">Color is rewritten so that it can deal with multiple images. Now it uses color table waves implemented in Igor 7 instead of color index waves. Not only names but also images of color tables are listed in the panel so that you can take a look at many color scales at once.</new>
		<new rev="937-939,942,943,945,949-954,962,964,970,971,982,998,999,1006,1020,1066,1083">Range is rewritten so that it can deal with multiple images.</new>
		<new rev="1030,1032-1034">Line subtraction now supports second order.</new>
		<chg rev="1022,1029">Some keyboard shortcuts were added or modified. The functionality assigned to F2 was moved to F8 because F2 is used to change names in the Data Browser.</chg>
		<chg rev="904">The close button of the info bar is now removed. The info bar can be closed from the right-click menu.</chg>
		<chg rev="876,877,886,890,947">Some obsolete functionalities of KM were deleted or replaced with those of Igor 7.</chg>
		<chg rev="867 and many">Changes required and/or optimized for Igor Pro 7.</chg><!--867,870,871,879-881,899,905,908,909,911-914,922,923,925,940,944,963,966,975-->
		<chg rev="869 and many">Small modifications.</chg><!--869,878,883,884,891-896,898,906,910,921,926-930,933,935,936,941,961,983-997,1011,1013-1016,1018,1019,1021,1024-1027,1031,1035,1038,1039,1041,1042,1044,1045,1047-1053,1062,1063,1065,1071-1074,1079-1081,1085-->
		<bug rev="958-960,969,971">Now SyncLayer works without a target window focused.</bug>
		<bug rev="888,889,931,932,934,956,957,1082">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-01-25 15:20 +0900" rev="981">
		<bug rev="981">Fixed a bug in the mouse coordinates. Even when (x,y) was selected, (r,t) was displayed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-01-23 17:50 +0900" rev="980">
		<bug rev="980">Fixed a bug that sxm and nsp files of Nanonis with a multi-lines comment could not be correctly loaded.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2017-01-06 17:12 +0900" rev="978">
		<chg rev="926">The mouse coordinates in a window are now available for date and time.</chg>
		<chg rev="919,924">Small modifications</chg>
		<bug rev="976,977">Fixed a bug in LineSpectra and LineProfile in displaying a wave taken in the MLS mode.</bug>
		<bug rev="920">Avoided a crash of Igor Pro when a line in a graph was duplicated.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2016-03-10 18:10 +0900" rev="918">
		<bug rev="918"><strong>Fourier transform returned a wave with a wrong offset in the y-direction. This bug occurred when an input wave has a y-delta different from a x-delta.</strong> In other words, this bug did nothing for data taken in a square with the same number of pixels in x and y. This bug was introduced in rev. 315.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2016-03-03 20:55 +0900" rev="917">
		<bug rev="916,917">Fixed a bug in loading Nanonis 3ds file of linecut data. This bug was related to strict checking of wave index bounds and introduced in rev. 868.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2016-02-04 21:10 +0900" rev="907">
		<chg rev="901">The control bar (information bar) can be closed from the right-click menu. The close button will be removed in the near future.</chg>
		<chg rev="885,900,902,907">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="875,887,897">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2016-01-25 20:05 +0900" rev="874">
		<chg rev="868">Loading Nanonis 3ds files works faster than before.</chg>
		<bug rev="872,873">Fixed bugs occuring in renaming or duplicating a window while Sync Layers, Sync Axis Range, or Sync Cursors work.</bug>
		<bug rev="866">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2016-01-13 13:50 +0900" rev="864">
		<chg rev="854,857">Modified the panel of position recorder.</chg>
		<chg rev="849,851,852,858,859,862,863">The procedure files of KM are hidden (not listed in the Windows &#62; Procedures submenu) unless you set to show them in the preference panel.</chg>
		<chg rev="853,855,856,860,861,864">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="850">Fixed a bug in Mac that an error occurred in displaying a 2D wave or a 3D wave.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-12-01 19:55 +0900" rev="848">
		<bug rev="848">The right-click menu of Line Profile and Line Spectra did not work correctly.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-11-26 20:30 +0900" rev="847">
		<chg rev="845-847">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="844">Fixed a bug that the right-click menu was slowly opened in a graph where a large wave was displayed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-11-24 21:05 +0900" rev="843">
		<new rev="838">update.bat for Windows was added. This bat file updates the macro files except those in the extension folder. (In other words, you can store your own files in the extension folder.) Note that this file is available unless you have moved the WaveMetrics folder from the Documents folder.</new>
		<new rev="829,832,834,835">More than 50 new color scales were added. Most of them were imported from <a href="http://reference.wolfram.com/language/guide/ColorSchemes.html">the Wolfram color schemes</a></new>
		<new rev="826,828,830">Color scales in the extension folder is now also loaded as those in the ctab folder. You can place your own color scales in the extension folder.</new>
		<chg rev="817">Linear interpolation, instead of a value of the nearest point, is now used in Fourier Symmetrization.</chg>
		<chg rev="815,819-825,827,831,833,837,839,841-843">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="816,818,836,839,840">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-10-19 20:20 +0900" rev="814">
		<bug rev="809-814">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-07-30 20:55 +0900" rev="808">
		<chg rev="807">The z value in the information bar now reflects magnitude, real, imaginary, and phase when a complex wave is displayed.</chg>
		<chg rev="805">Requires Igor Pro ver. 6.37. The quick hacks for Igor Pro ver. 6.36 were removed.</chg>
		<chg rev="804,808">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="806"><strong>Complex, imaginary, and phase of Fourier transform were incorrect.</strong>
			Although the right half was correct, it was not correctly symmetrized to the left half.
			Fourier transform of a real function satisfies F(k) = F<sup>*</sup>(-k), but the right half was symmetrized without taking complex conjugate for complex and multiplying -1 for imaginary and phase.
		</bug>
		<bug rev="803">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-05-08 17:45 +0900" rev="802">
		<chg rev="802">To restart KM, choose &#34;KM&#34; with the shift key pressed and you will find &#34;Restart KM&#34; at the bottom of the menu.</chg>
		<chg rev="802">When you can not load a file via drag and drop, try &#34;KM &#62; Load Data... &#62; Reset BeforeFileOpenHook&#34; if this item is displayed. This is for a bug of Igor Pro ver. 6.36.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-04-14 14:40 +0900" rev="801">
		<new rev="781,784-787,792-798,800">Sync Axis Range is implemented. Axis ranges of multiple graphs are synchronized.</new>
		<new rev="780,784-787,789,791-798,800">Multiple synchronization groups are now available in Sync Layer and Sync Cursor. For example, graph 1 and 2 can be synchronized independently of graph 3 and 4 that are already in sync.</new>
		<new rev="771,772,775,776.783">End effects are implemented for Fourier Filter.</new>
		<new rev="765-767,790,791">Spectrum Viewer now works with not only the mouse cursor but also cursor A.</new>
		<chg rev="799">Multiple Line Spectra can share one target window. For example, a topograph can be a target window of Line Spectra of current and dI/dV.</chg>
		<chg rev="777">The peak search of Fourier Symmetrization from the marquee menu is now available for 3D waves.</chg>
		<chg rev="769">Multipass settings of Nanonis are now saved as a wave in the settings datafolder.</chg>
		<chg rev="763,770,773,774,778,801">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="788">Range and Color did not work for Line Spectra and Line profile.</bug>
		<bug rev="779">Fixed a bug that a wave was not displayed in a new window but appended to an existing window.</bug>
		<bug rev="768">An error occurred when space without any table items was right-clicked.</bug>
		<bug rev="766">Sync Cursor did not work correctly when cursors were in the free mode and the synchronization was in the xy mode.</bug>
		<bug rev="764">Coordinates at the mouse cursor were not correctly taken when dimension of a wave is 1 in either x or y direction.</bug>
		<bug rev="762">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-03-10 12:35 +0900" rev="761">
		<new rev="750-752">Position Recorder. You can record index coordinates (p and q) where you click.</new>
		<new rev="745,746">Export Graphics (Transparent) is added. This is similar to &#34;Edit &#62; Export Graphics...&#34;, but makes a clipboard copy of trace/image with transparent background. You can choose some options from &#34;KM &#62; Preference&#34;.</new>
		<new rev="734,737,748">SpectrumViewer (Point spectrum) is renewed.
			<sub>
				<item>A spectrum viewer can have multiple target windows. For example, both dI/dV and topograph windows can be target windows of a spectrum viewer.</item>
				<item>A window can be target windows of multiple spectrum viewers. For example, a topograph window can be a target window of dI/dV and current windows.</item>
				<item>New spectrum viewer no longer uses a temporary datafolder except for Nanonis MLS waves.</item>
			</sub>
		</new>
		<chg rev="757">The panel of Fourier filter is now resizable.</chg>
		<chg rev="735,736,739-743,749,753,755,756,761">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="760"><strong>The z value displayed in LayerViewer was not correct.</strong> The displayed value was always taken from 0th layer.</bug>
		<bug rev="759">Window selection of SyncLayer did not work correctly when a window not displaying an image existed.</bug>
		<bug rev="758">3-layer waves were treated as three plane images when they were displayed.</bug>
		<bug rev="754"><strong>When cross correlation was calculated, locations of maximum and minimum displayed in the history area were wrong.</strong></bug>
		<bug rev="747">Keyboard shortcuts of Image and Layer Viewers did not work just after those windows were opened.</bug>
		<bug rev="743">In the panel of &#34;Save Graphics (Layers)&#34;, resolution of 4X, 5X, and 8X screen was not correctly reflected to the command.</bug>
		<bug rev="738">The keyboard shortcut to expand or shrink a window was incorrect.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-02-26 14:35 +0900" rev="733">
		<bug rev="733">"Save Graphics" in the File menu could not sometimes be selected.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-02-25 18:10 +0900" rev="732">
		<bug rev="732">Auto range did not work correctly when an axis range was expanded.</bug>
		<bug rev="731">Fixed a bug that coordinations at the mouse cursor for 1D traces did not work correctly.</bug>
		<chg rev="729">Improved multiple selection of waves in Preview.</chg>
		<chg rev="730">Small modifications.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-02-24 18:00 +0900" rev="728">
		<chg rev="724-726,728">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="727">Target windows of LineSpectra could be not changed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-01-19 20:00 +0900" rev="723">
		<bug rev="722,723">Small bug fixes.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-01-15 21:30 +0900" rev="721">
		<new rev="719-721">Nanonis 3ds file header can be saved as a csv file.</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2015-01-06 14:15 +0900" rev="718">
		<new rev="714,715">Actual coordinates can be shown in the control bar even when a field of view is rotated.</new>
		<new rev="672-690,692,699,701,703-705,707,708,713">LayerViewer is renewed. Now you can rename and duplicate a window of LayerViewer. New LayerViewer no longer uses a temporary datafolder.</new>
		<new rev="706,710">When you start the macro, it is automatically checked whether new version is available.</new>
		<new rev="671">Preview is renewed. A list of waves are made by entering a search query.</new>
		<chg rev="662-670,691,693-698,700,702,709,711,712,716-718">Small modifications.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2014-09-26 18:00 +0900" rev="661">
		<chg rev="654-661">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug>WMImageInfo.ipf included in Igor Pro 6.35A5 has a bug.
			Replace it with the file in the KM package.
			WMImageInfo.ipf is found at \Igor Pro Folder\WaveMetrics Procedures\Image and Contour Plots.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2014-09-18 17:25 +0900" rev="653">
		<chg rev="646">Fourier filter got slightly faster.</chg>
		<chg rev="642-645,647,650-653">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug>If you use Igor Pro 6.35A, replace Graph Utility Procs.ipf with the file included in the KM package.
			Graph Utility Procs.ipf is found at \Igor Pro Folder\WaveMetrics Procedures\Graphing.
		</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2014-07-17 13:30 +0900" rev="641">
		<chg rev="633,634,640,641">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="632,631">Fourier transform and Fourier symmetrization got slightly faster.</chg>
		<bug rev="639">The checkbox of &#34;show only trace #&#34; could not be checked.</bug>
		<bug rev="635,638">Restored changes made in rev. 615.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2013-10-02 14:35 +0900" rev="630">
		<bug rev="629">Height of LayerViewer was too small when a n&#215;1&#215;m wave was displayed.</bug>
		<bug rev="627">The Macro could not be restarted when #include &#34;All KM Procedures&#34; in the procedure window was manually deleted.</bug>
		<bug rev="626,628">3ds files taken with an older version(s) of Nanonis software could not be loaded.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2013-07-08 16:25 +0900" rev="623">
		<bug rev="623">An error occurred in loading an .nsp file.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2013-07-03 13:00 +0900" rev="622">
		<bug rev="621">Name of top graph could been changed when first compiling after opening an experiment file was done.</bug>
		<bug rev="620">Improved backward compatibility of LineProfile.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2013-06-27 21:05 +0900" rev="619">
		<new>Major improvements and new features on Nanonis-file loading.
			<sub>
				<item rev="560-562,566,574,589,590,592,595">Supported the MLS mode of bias spectroscopy.</item>
				<item rev="609">.nsp files (Long Term Spectrum) can be loaded.</item>
				<item rev="554">All experiment types of .dat file (not only Bias- and Z- spectroscopy but also Generic sweep, Spectrum, History data, etc.) can be loaded.</item>
				<item rev="554-557">.dat and .3ds files of Bias spectroscopy without the lock-in header module can be loaded. Processes related to the lock-in header module such as conversion to dI/dV are just skipped if the module is not included.</item>
				<item rev="604,607">Supported Z-modulation (dI/dZ) in .dat and .3ds files.</item>
				<item rev="587">.sxm files of downward scan can be correctly loaded.</item>
				<item rev="577">.sxm files without the scan header module can be correctly loaded. (Dependence on the scan header module was resolved.)</item>
				<item rev="586,597-599">Waves are named in the same manner for .sxm, .dat, and .3ds files.</item>
				<item rev="578,582-585,600,601">All header items are saved as global variables.</item>
			</sub>
		</new>
		<new rev="602,606,611,612">Setup conditions, displayed area, and graph name as well as wave name can be chosen as a graph title.</new>
		<chg rev="615">Some windows can not be closed when the macro is not complied in order to prevent unanticipated errors.</chg>
		<chg rev="563-574,617">Panels of Spectrum Viewer, Line Spectra, and Line Profile were simplified. Menu items are now appear if you right-click on the panel control.</chg>
		<chg rev="558,559,579-581,588,591,594,596,603,605,610,613,614,616,618">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="593">A resultant wave of plane subtraction was not displayed even if the display checkbox of the panel was checked.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-12-27 16:15 +0900" rev="553">
		<new rev="546">"End effect" was implemented for Fourier symmetrization. "Wrap" was used for previous versions, but now default is "Zero". If you want to have the same results as before, you have to explicitly choose "Wrap".</new>
		<chg rev="547-553">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="545">When you reload a data file into an experiment file, you will be asked to enter a new name for a datafolder.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-11-14 21:55 +0900" rev="544">
		<new rev="529, 530">A peak position for "Fourier symmetrization..." can be obtained by a Lorentzian fitting. Click "vector 1" (or 2) in the panel, enclose a peak by graph marquee, right click the enclosed area, and you will see a menu to do fitting.</new>
		<new rev="509, 520, 521">Made a list of shortcuts available from KM > Help > Shortcuts. Some shortcuts were added.</new>
		<new rev="511, 513">Made a batch file to install or update the macro. This is available for Windows Vista or later and if "Igor Pro 6 User Files" folder exists under My Documents as default.</new>
		<new rev="498, 500, 503, 504">Coefficients of 1st-order plane subtraction can be calculated about a square region. This would be useful when you want to subtract a plane from an image containing steps. The region can be specified by the panel of Subtraction or the graph marquee (and right-clicking inside the marquee).</new>
		<new rev="481, 482, 485-487">Range and Color are now available for images in the panels of Line Spectra and Line Profile.</new>
		<chg rev="539">"fast scan" in the panel of Fourier symmetrization was changed to "shear". The corresponding optional parameter of KMFourierSym was also changed from "scan" to "shear". This is because a primal factor is not scan direction but actual shear direction, which may be effectively determined by scan direction. See also the help of "Fourier symmetrization..." available from the button of the panel.</chg>
		<chg rev="528, 531">When "show only trace" is checked, name of a displayed trace and a fitted wave (if any) are also displayed.</chg>
		<chg rev="527">Fourier transform of a 2D wave got slightly faster (~10%).</chg>
		<chg rev="524, 526">Selected menu items in the panel of Fourier transform appear as default next time you open the panel.</chg>
		<chg rev="522">Simplified Spectrum Viewer. When a source wave is complex, a displayed spectrum is also complex.</chg>
		<chg rev="502">The incremental mode of KMSubtraction was deleted.</chg>
		<chg rev="501">Fixed a problem that command strings created by panels of KMFilter and KMFourierSym could not be used as they were. This is related to a bug of Igor Pro 6.22A.</chg>
		<chg rev="489, 499, 505">Output type and name of window function are recorded as note of an FFT wave.</chg>
		<chg rev="479, 480, 483, 484, 490, 495, 497, 504, 506, 507, 511, 518, 521, 523, 536, 538, 540-544">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="539"><strong>When y-direction was chosen as fast scan direction (now shear direction) in Fourier symmetrization, calculation was incorrect.</strong></bug>
		<bug rev="534, 535, 537">Avoided an issue that ImageLineProfile can return a line profile with an extra NaN point or a while line with NaN.</bug>
		<bug rev="533">An extracted layer was not correctly displayed when a subwindow was opened.</bug>
		<bug rev="532">A panel to extract layers could be multiply opened.</bug>
		<bug rev="522">Spectrum Viewer did not work correctly when a source wave has a specific name.</bug>
		<bug rev="510">Even when you changed the layer index, the displayed z-values were still those of the 1st layer (index 0).</bug>
		<bug rev="508">Foreground color was white even for white background when a subwindow was opened.</bug>
		<bug rev="494">Modified behaviors when a fitting of KMSubtraction fails.</bug>
		<bug rev="488">A name of a wave can be changed when the wave is displayed with autorange (e.g. 0.5%).</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-10-02 17:20 +0900" rev="478">
		<chg rev="478">Documents were updated.</chg>
		<chg rev="477">Fitting parameters of Exp and Log (KMSubtraction) are recorded as wave note.</chg>
		<bug rev="478"><strong>x- and y-scaling of waves created by Exp- and Log- modes of KMSubtraction were incorrect.</strong></bug>
		<bug rev="476">Update check did not work correctly.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-10-01 17:15 +0900" rev="475">
		<chg rev="475">Documents were updated.</chg>
		<new rev="474, 475">Added "Log" to KMSubtraction. This is a logarithmic version of "Exp". This often works better than "Exp".</new>
		<bug rev="475">The echo string by KMSubtraction(mode=1) was incorrect.</bug>
		<bug rev="473">When a wave was opened by Layerviewer, the name of the wave could be changed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-09-27 22:50 +0900" rev="472">
		<new rev="465, 471">Implemented a new algorithm to remove background with heavy z-piezo creep prominent in long-time topographic images such as those simultaneously taken with conductance maps. An old one ("y-exp") was substituted with this.</new>
		<new rev="457, 464, 469">An image file can be saved from right-clicking the control bar, "Window > Save Graphics...". Images files of layers can be also saved from "Windows > Save Graphics (Layers)...". The latter was included in a tag of "Extract Layers". This would reduce distance your mouse cursor travels to select the menu items at the top left corner of the Igor window.</new>
		<chg rev="463">Axis ranges are also synchronized when cursors are synchronized.</chg>
		<chg rev="461">The auto range (e.g. "0.5%") can be turned off by selecting (unchecking) the right-click menu item.</chg>
		<chg rev="460">The auto range is now calculated about not the whole wave but the displayed area. See what happens when you expand an image with the auto range on.</chg>
		<chg rev="454, 459, 462, 466-468, 472">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="458">Fixed a bug in synchronizing cursors.</bug>
		<bug rev="456">Fixed a bug in KMFilter() occuring when name of a destination wave was not specified.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-03-21 21:15 +0900" rev="453">
		<bug rev="453">The mouse coordinates for 2D and 3D waves were not correctly displayed. This bug was included in the last update yesterday.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-03-17 14:50 +0900" rev="452">
		<new rev="444">Added KMTraceColor(). Each trace can be colored differently based on a color table.</new>
		<new rev="436, 438, 439, 446, 451">A control bar is now displayed for a window displaying 1D traces. Operations for 1D traces or waves such as Offset or Workfunction are invoked by right-clicking the control bar in the same manner for 2D/3D waves.</new>
		<chg rev="444">Renamed KMOffset to KMTraceOffset.</chg>
		<chg rev="435, 440, 442, 445, 452">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="434, 447">Expanded the area where the mouse coordinates are available in a graph. Now it is available not only on the top image but also inside the axis range for the top image.</chg>
		<bug rev="450">The echo shown in the history area by Histogram was not correct.</bug>
		<bug rev="449">Incremental-order plane-subtraction did not work.</bug>
		<bug rev="448">Offsets (DimOffset) of Fourier-filtered 2D wave were not the same as the original wave.</bug>
		<bug rev="446">The "Free" checkbox in the panel of coordination settings was always checked before it was unchecked once even if it should have been unchecked.</bug>
		<bug rev="441">Fixed a bug which occurred when the source 3D wave was deleted with SpectrumViewer opened.</bug>
		<bug rev="437">Fixed a bug related to rev. 420.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-02-01 15:50 +0900" rev="433">
		<bug rev="433">When KMLoadData() received a wrong path, it was aborted without showing an error message.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-01-31 20:25 +0900" rev="432">
		<new rev="431">Added KMMoveWindowsIn(). When you open an experiment file in a small monitor (e. g., a laptop), you can not often reach some graphs put outside of your monitor. (This occurs when you or a person who saved the experiment file used a monitor bigger than yours.) This function works to move those graphs inside your monitor. This can be executed from menubar > KM > Extension > Move Windows In.</new>
		<chg rev="432">Documents were updated.</chg>
		<chg rev="430">The behavior of ColorScale when the window size is not fixed was improved.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2012-01-17 13:55 +0900" rev="427">
		<chg rev="422-427">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="421">Out-of-range index was referred when the last layer was saved into a file from LayerViewer.</bug>
		<bug rev="420">Mouse coordinates can be correctly picked up when the left and bottom axes are swapped.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-11-09 10:55 +0900" rev="419">
		<chg rev="419">Now the page up key and the page down key are used for changing the index of LayerViewer. To expand or shrink a window, use those keys with the ctrl key (Win) or the command key (Mac) pressed.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-11-08 10:40 +0900" rev="418">
		<bug rev="418">The shift key did not work in loading files when Igor Pro was not activated.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-11-01 20:00 +0900" rev="416">
		<new rev="408, 415">"Normalized magnitude" and "Normalized magnitude squared" are added to Fourier transform.</new>
		<new rev="409, 410, 412">Added a file loader for Nanonis dat files. The average (fwd/2+bwd/2) wave and the subtraction (fwd-bwd) wave are created. When the shift key is pressed, the original forward and backward sweeps are saved without taking the average.</new>
		<chg rev="411, 412">The type of waves created from Nanonis sxm files and Nanonis 3ds files was changed from double precision to single precision.</chg>
		<chg rev="400-402, 413-416">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="399">The right-click menu item of Fourier transform could be chosen even for a wave containing NaN and INF.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-09-09 18:23 +0900" rev="398">
		<chg rev="398">Documents were updated.</chg>
		<chg rev="397">Tiny modifications in Load3ds.ipf.</chg>
		<chg rev="395, 396">Changed LoadSXM to the new format of data-loading functions.</chg>
		<bug rev="393">Fixed a bug in LoadSM2. An error occured when multiple pages of spectral data, for example dI/dV and I-V, are contained in a file,</bug>
	</up>
	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-09-08 16:15 +0900" rev="392">
		<chg rev="392">Documents were updated.</chg>
		<chg rev="389, 390">If ctrl (Win) or cmd (Mac) is pressed when a data file is loaded, waves created by a data-loading function are displayed.</chg>
		<chg rev="387, 388, 391">Changed Load3ds to the new format of data-loading functions. Also it became faster.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-09-07 21:55 +0900" rev="386">
		<new rev="321, 370">Added "level" to the panel of Range.</new>
		<new rev="335-337, 347, 364-369, 374, 383">You can put the command to the command line or the clipboard by choosing "To" popupmenu of the panels of Fourier Filter, Fourier, Subtraction, Correlation, Histogram, WaveStats, and Workfunction</new>
		<new rev="333, 334">Added Fourier Symmetrization. This symmetrizes Fourier transform based on the symmetry of lattice.</new>
		<chg rev="378, 379, 381, 385">Data-loading functions are now required to receive a string and return a wave. The string parameter is the absolute path to a file. The return wave is a wave created by the data-loading function. See "Function List.txt" for details.</chg>
		<chg rev="376, 377">KMWaveStats accepts a wave having wave references. See also <a href="cmdlist.html#KMWavesStats"> the Command List</a>.</chg>
		<chg rev="340, 352, 371, 384">Menu items were rearranged in a semantic order.</chg>
		<chg rev="336, 347, 364-369, 374, 383">The source wave is now not optional but required in Fourier, Subtraction, Correlation, Histogram, WaveStats, and Workfunction.</chg>
		<chg rev="351">"property" in the right-click menu was renamed to "data parameters".</chg>
		<chg rev="347">The result of subtraction can be saved to a new wave instead of overwriting the source wave.</chg>
		<chg rev="345, 346">KMTrim was removed because it could be totally replaced with Duplicate/O/R.</chg>
		<chg rev="340">A popupmenu was added to select a component of a complex wave to be displayed in Layer Viewer.</chg>
		<chg rev="340">The function to show the layer value (energy) in Layer Viewer was renamed to "Auto Annotation" and now can be directly chosen from the right-click menu. Since this new version is not compatible with the previous versions, you will need to recreate the annotation with new version.</chg>
		<chg rev="322, 324-331, 338, 339, 341-344, 346, 348, 353-363, 365, 368, 373, 375, 380, 382, 385, 386">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="350">Fixed a bug that out-of-range coordinates could be obtained in Image Viewer and etc.</bug>
		<bug rev="349">Fixed a problem that the shortcuts of Range (F4), Color (F5), and Subtraction (F6) could be invoked even if the target window was not the top window.</bug>
		<bug rev="332">Fixed an error occurring when the Layer Viewer was clicked with the "NVAR SVAR WAVE Checking" checked.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-06-29 17:21 +0900" rev="323">
		<bug rev="323">Fixed an error occurring when the top window contained no image, the menu bar was clicked, and "NVAR SVAR WAVE Checking" in the Procedure menu as checked.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-06-24 18:00 +0900" rev="320">
		<new rev="318-320">Added statistics in z direction to KMWavesStats. This is available for 3D waves.</new>
		<bug rev="317">Fixed a bug that some help files could not be opened.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-06-23 15:30 +0900" rev="316">
		<bug rev="316">Fixed a bug of the panels of Range and Color. They were not opened correctly through the shortcuts when another panel was opened in front of the target window.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-06-21 21:15 +0900" rev="315">
		<new rev="312-315">Added Fourier Filter.</new>
		<new rev="305">Added a new command "KMSyncLayer". This synchronizes layer index of multiple LayerViewers. This was available by "option" of the context menu of LayerViewer, but now the menu was reorganized.</new>
		<chg rev="298, 306">Fourier, Correlation, and Workfunction got much faster. This is salient on a machine with multiple cores and for 3D waves. For example, with 4 cores and for a 256&#215;256&#215;81 wave, Fourier, Correlation, and Workfunction got &#215;4, &#215;6, and &#215;80 faster than before, respectively.</chg>
		<chg rev="299, 301">"KMCursorSync" was renamed to "KMSyncCursor".</chg>
		<chg rev="300, 307">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="297">A wave of chisq is saved for Workfunction fitting of a 3D I-z wave.</chg>
		<bug rev="311">Fixed an bug of Offset that "hidden line elimination" was turned on even when it was actually off.</bug>
		<bug rev="308">Fixed an error in loading a color table "Wrapangle2".</bug>
		<bug rev="302-304">Fixed an error in opening panels of Color and Range with a specific condition.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-05-30 12:00 +0900" rev="296">
		<bug rev="296">An error occurred when a wave having name same as that of a color table to be loaded existed in the current datafolder.</bug>
		<new rev="295">Added a color table "Wrapangle2"</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-05-26 14:40 +0900" rev="294">
		<chg rev="290-292">Added "Properties" to the context menu of LayerViewer and ImageViewer. This shows a list of variables and their values in the setting datafolder. The variable list by clicking the control bar with pressing ctrl key was deleted.</chg>
		<bug rev="294">3D waves with 1 data point in the column (y) direction were not displayed by LayerViewer.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-05-11 18:30 +0900" rev="287">
		<bug rev="287">Fixed a problem that KM did not start up on Igor Pro 6.2.2.0.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-03-10 19:35 +0900" rev="286">
		<bug rev="286">An error occurred when a window having duplicated traces was closed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-03-07 17:35 +0900" rev="285">
		<bug rev="284, 285">Conversion from V to nS was not done for standard deviation waves created by LoadSM2.ipf.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-02-23 21:15 +0900" rev="283">
		<bug rev="283">An error occurred when a color table of Igor Pro was changed to another table by Color with "NVAR SVAR WAVE Checking" in the Procedure menu checked. The same error could occur when a layer was extracted by LayerViewer because Color is used.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-02-23 11:35 +0900" rev="282">
		<bug rev="281">An error occurred when no wave existed in the current datafolder, no wave was selected in the databrowser, and "Display Data" was selected.</bug>
		<bug rev="281">An error occurred when the name of wave shown in LayerViewer was changed with "NVAR SVAR WAVE Checking" in the Procedure menu checked.</bug>
		<bug rev="280">The echo of Correlation was not returned in the history area.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-02-18 22:17 +0900" rev="278">
		<bug rev="278">An error occurred when some KM menu items are selected with "NVAR SVAR WAVE Checking" in the Procedure menu checked.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-02-17 21:25 +0900" rev="277">
		<bug rev="277">An error due to attempting to open a file already opened occurred when KM was complied on the 2nd instance of Igor Pro.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-02-15 20:50 +0900" rev="275">
		<bug rev="273, 274">A compile error occurred when an experiment file created on an OS (e.g. Windows XP) was opened on another OS (e.g. Windows 7).</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2011-01-03 21:20 +0900" rev="271">
		<bug rev="271">A 1D wave was not displayed when KMDisplay was invoked from not the menu but the command line.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-12-30 18:40 +0900" rev="270">
		<bug rev="267, 268">Color, Line Profile, Line Spectra, and Range did not work when the name of target wave was long.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-12-24 20:50 +0900" rev="264">
		<new rev="253, 254">"Expansion" of a window can be changed by pressing "Page Up" and "Page Down" keys.</new>
		<new rev="212, 214-216, 226, 227, 229-233, 256, 258">Right-click the control bar of ImageViewer and LayerViewer to do something like "Range", "Color", and "Subtraction". When you select a menu item of "KM", a panel to select a wave in the current datafolder is shown. This is probably the biggest change ever in the way to use KM. I would say that you will get used to this way soon although you may be confused a bit for a moment. I hope you like this changeover.</new>
		<new rev="203">An intensity plot and profile are shown in the panel of KMFFT.</new>
		<new rev="199">Added window functions for FFT. Formula of each function is written in the manual of Igor Pro. See help of "FFT"</new>
		<chg rev="253">The modifier key to expand or shrink axis ranges (introduced in rev. 152) was changed from alt(Win)/option(Mac) to Ctrl(Win)/Command(Mac).</chg>
		<chg rev="251">Updating coordinates in Info bar and LayerViewer is suppressed when shift key is pressed.</chg>
		<chg rev="246-249, 255">Independent axis ranges are used for traces and an image in the panel of Line Profile and Line Spectra. This is particularly useful when you change the axis range of the vertical axis.</chg>
		<chg rev="243">Checking update of KM (menubar > Help > Update for KM rev. ***) can be done without launching a web browser.</chg>
		<chg rev="240">The behavior of "Display" and "Preview" (menu bar) was changed. When a wave is selected in the Data Browser, its trace or image is shown. When no wave is selected, the panel of Preview is shown. The menu item of "Preview" was deleted.</chg>
		<chg rev="234, 250">When multiple 1D waves are selected in the Data Browser, they are shown together in one window.</chg>
		<chg rev="217">White letters are used for Color Scale when background color is dark.</chg>
		<chg rev="200-202, 205, 209-211, 214, 218-225, 228, 235-238, 241, 244, 245, 252, 260">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="263">Window size was not correctly inherited from LayerViewer to a window where an extracted layer is shown when the expansion of LayerViewer was not 1.</bug>
		<bug rev="242">Fixed an incorrect behavior occurred when "display text markers beside the trajectory" of Line Profile and Line Spectra is checked.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-11-23 17:55 +0900" rev="196">
		<chg rev="183-187, 189, 190, 195">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="182, 184-186, 195">Requires Igor Pro 6.2.</chg>
		<chg rev="182">Added new buttons in the panels of LineProfile and LineSpectra to change positions of the two end points and to put one point at the center of the image. This was implemented as short cuts.</chg>
		<bug rev="194">An error occurred when a cursor was removed from a graph during synchronizing cursor positions.</bug>
		<bug rev="193">Cursor Sync did not work properly in the p mode.</bug>
		<bug rev="192">Some panels was not able to be closed by pressing esc key.</bug>
		<bug rev="188">The echo command of Color (shown in the history area) was incorrect.</bug>
	</up>
	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-09-09 20:15 +0900" rev="181">
		<bug rev="181">The panels of Line Spectra and Line Profile flickered and stopped working when ctrl + arrow key was pressed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-09-07 22:30 +0900" rev="179">
		<chg rev="174">The coordinates in the control bar of the 2D and 3D wave viewer are aligned left. This makes it possible to reduce the default size of the viewer from 260 to 240.</chg>
		<chg rev="173">The histogram in the panel of Range is adjusted to the range of the bottom axis.</chg>
		<chg rev="169">Added "subtract" parameter to KMFFT(). Now average of a wave can be subtracted before computing FFT. It was possible if you used the panel of KMFFT, but now it can be from the command line as well. See also <a href="cmdlist.html#KMFFT">the command list</a></chg>
		<chg rev="164, 168, 170, 177, 178">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="172">In the panel of Workfunction, the limitation of the fitting range was not cleared when the "auto" was checked.</bug>
		<bug rev="171">Several panels couldn't be opened for several specific parameters due to improper error check.</bug>
		<bug rev="166">The result wave wasn't displayed even when "display" of the panel of Histogram was checked.</bug>
		<bug rev="165">The progress bar didn't work properly when a hidden panel existed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-09-03 16:30 +0900" rev="163">
		<chg rev="159-161">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="162">Several panels couldn't be properly opened when a hidden panel existed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-08-27 23:00 +0900" rev="158">
		<new rev="157">Update check is available from the menu.</new>
		<new rev="152">Expand/Shrink the axis range in the 2D and 3D wave viewer by mouse wheel with alt(Win)/option(Mac).</new>
		<new rev="145, 146">When an absolute path to a folder is passed to KMLoadData, it loads files in the folder and all subfolder.</new>
		<new rev="126, 128-130, 154">Added automatic adjustment of z range of an image to Range. When the source wave of the image is modified (e.g. Subtraction), the z range is now automatically adjusted to the modified wave.</new>
		<new rev="117, 131, 133, 134, 138-140"><a href="cmdlist.html">Command List of KM</a>, written in both English and Japanese, is available on the web. Select "Command List" of the menu.</new>
		<chg rev="156">The change log was moved to the web from Dropbox, and is available from the menu of KM.</chg>
		<chg rev="143">How to include procedure files was changed. Procedure scan errors may occur when you open existing experiment files. You can fix these errors as follows. In the error dialogs, (1) change #include "Include KM Procedures" to #include "All KM Procedures" and click the Retry button, (2) delete #include "Include File Procedures.ipf" and click the Retry button, (3) delete #include "Include Ext Procedures.ipf" and click the Retry button.</chg>
		<chg rev="141, 142, 144, 150">Modified the menu items. Unified "KM" and "Tools" to "KM", added "Restart KM" and "Extension", removed "About", added "Color" submenu, and placed "Color table" and "Color scale" under "Color".</chg>
		<chg rev="135">Removed KMRotate because its functionality can be done by a native function of Igor Pro (MaxtixOP).</chg>
		<chg rev="132">Renamed KMCrop to KMTrim.</chg>
		<chg rev="127, 137">Removed "auto scale" from the 3D wave viewer because similar and a superior function was implemented to Range. Related to this modification, an error dialog saying "While executing LoadPackagePreferences, the following error occurred: The package preference file is corrupt. You should delete it" may appear once. This dialog appears due to a bug of Igor Pro which will be fixed in next release (ver. 6.20).</chg>
		<chg rev="118">The histogram of Range is updated when the source wave is changed such as in changing the index of the 3D wave viewer.</chg>
		<chg rev="112-116, 119-125, 151">Changed UI of the 3D wave viewer, the 2D wave viewer, Range, and Offset.</chg>
		<chg rev="92, 107, 108, 111, 136, 147-149">Small modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="90, 91, 153, 155, 158">Updated documents.</chg>
		<bug rev="118">Fixed a bug that range of z values was changed when the option panel of Range was opened.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-04-08 19:42 +0900" rev="110">
		<bug rev="110">Fixed a bug that KMWaveStats did not give a result for 1D waves.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-04-06 17:00 +0900" rev="109">
		<bug rev="109">Fixed a bug that waves under root data folder were deleted when a panel such as LayerViewer was closed.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2010-03-12 20:19 +0900" rev="105">
		<bug rev="105">Fixed a bug in the panel of KMWorkfunction.</bug>
		<chg rev="82, 84, 95-104">Small modifications. Note that KMKillTmpDfs is obsolete. Use KMonClosePnl or Free Data Folder.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-12-16 16:04 +0900" rev="94">
		<chg rev="94">Made Cursor Sync unselectable when no graph was displayed.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-11-18 10:00 +0900" rev="88">
		<bug rev="88">Fix a problem (made in update on 2009-08-28) that Rotate did not work for 3D waves.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-09-01 0:06 +0900" rev="81">
		<chg rev="81">Removed the expand button and the zero bars in the control bar of Trace Offset.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-31 21:38 +0900" rev="80">
		<bug rev="80">Fixed that the expand button did not work correctly when height of graph was absolute.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-31 10:50 +0900" rev="79">
		<bug rev="79">Fixed a problem that panels of LineProfile and LineSpectra froze after first click.</bug>
		<chg rev="73-75, 77, 78">Small modifications.</chg>
		<bug rev="76">Fixed a wrong calculation of LayerSubtraction(mode=2) when the input wave was complex.</bug>
		<chg rev="72">Loading SM2 files became faster (~150%).</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-28 21:29 +0900" rev="71">
		<chg rev="66-71">Fourier and Correlation became a little faster.</chg>
		<chg rev="65">Changed UI of the progress bar.</chg>
		<chg rev="59-64">Internal modifications.</chg>
		<chg rev="56-58">Modified inputs of wave names in panels.</chg>
		<chg rev="55">Removed macro files for Igor Pro 6.05 because Igor Pro 6.11 had been released</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-25 13:56 +0900" rev="55">
		<bug rev="55">(For Igor Pro 6.1) Fixed incorrect behaviors of the panel of LayerViewer for outputting waves or files.</bug>
		<chg rev="54">Prepared macro files for both Igor Pro 6.1 and 6.05.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-24 18:04 +0900" rev="48">
		<chg rev="48">Restored macro files for Igor Pro 6.05 in order to avoid bugs in Igor Pro 6.1.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-18 22:30 +0900" rev="54">
		<chg rev="54">Added a note describing folders to install the macro files because those folder had been changed in Igor Pro 6.1.</chg>
		<bug rev="52, 53">Fixed that the macro sometimes could not be launched.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-08-04 14:40 +0900" rev="51">
		<new rev="51">The index value of LayerViewer can be changed by mouse wheel. (Requires Igor Pro 6.1)</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-06-15 15:40 +0900" rev="48">
		<chg rev="47">Made color of letters and lines in legend white when background was black.</chg>
		<chg rev="45">Wrote KMGetWindowInfo and removed KMGetBackgroundColor. If you use the latter in your own macros, use the former, which is more comprehensive than the latter.</chg>
		<bug rev="48">Fixed a bug of Color Scale that a parameter of "vertical" was always 0 even if it was explicitly designated 1.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-06-10 10:42 +0900" rev="44">
		<chg rev="44">Updated notes.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-06-09 16:48 +0900" rev="43">
		<new rev="43">Enabled transparent PNG in saving files from LayerViewer.</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-05-27 13:54 +0900" rev="41">
		<bug rev="41">Fixed a problem that a user's (neither Igor Pro nor Kohsaka Macro) color scale wave was deleted when KM Color panel was opened.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-04-17 11:43 +0900" rev="39">
		<chg rev="39">Internal modifications.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-04-06 21:10 +0900" rev="36">
		<new rev="13, 15, 29">Info bar can be added to a image which already displayed.</new>
		<chg rev="36">When a wave is extracted by LayerViewer, the note of the original wave is copied to the extracted wave.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-04-02 15:31 +0900" rev="34">
		<new rev="34">Cursor Sync is now available for a graph displaying 1D waves.</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-04-01 12:01 +0900" rev="32">
		<bug rev="32">Fixed a bug occurring when mouse cursor is outside of LayerViewer.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-03-09 23:23 +0900" rev="26">
		<new rev="10,14,17">Cursor Sync. Synchronize position of cursors in multiple windows.</new>
		<bug rev="26">Fixed an error when a layer was extracted by LayerViewer.</bug>
		<bug rev="25">Color didn't work for specific parameters.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-03-05 14:34 +0900" rev="21">
		<chg rev="21">A window function (triangle) for FFT was no longer necessary and removed because a bug of Igor Pro had been fixed.</chg>
		<chg rev="18, 19">Other menu items can be selected in the same way as Color scale etc.</chg>
		<bug rev="20">Fixed an error of the panel of Correlation.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-03-04 23:40 +0900" rev="16">
		<chg rev="16">Color scale, Color, and Range can be selected from the menu when the target window is the top window.</chg>
		<chg rev="11, 12">Deleted obsolete functions.</chg>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-03-03 21:34 +0900" rev="9">
		<bug rev="9">"KMLoadData()" is now printed in the history area before various informations given by KMLoadData.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-02-26 20:02 +0900" rev="6">
		<new rev="6">Axes can be added and removed from an image by right-clicking the control bar of LayerViewer and ImageViewer.</new>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" date="2009-02-25 22:33 +0900" rev="5">
		<new rev="3">Changed old 'invert' of Color to 'reverse' and added new 'invert'.</new>
		<chg rev="2">Cumulative modifications since ver. 0.971.</chg>
		<bug rev="5">Fixed a bug in Defect2.ibw</bug>
		<bug rev="4">Removed Defect3.ibw because it was 'inverted' Defect2.ibw.</bug>
	</up>

	<up author="kohsaka" rev="1">
		<new rev="1">Started new revision counting.</new>
	</up>
</log>
